That is the, it's such a, oh, what a dumb question.
The illegal aliens who are here are taking jobs away from blacks.
They're taking jobs away from whites.
They're taking jobs away from Latinos.
They're taking their health benefits away.
They're taking their school slots away.
And, of course, in many cases, they're committing heinous crimes.
We cannot have a system of law in this country that privileges illegal aliens over American citizens.
And that's what they're doing.
You know it, and I know it.
So that's not exactly a no, Stephen.
Can you just unequivocally state that the immigration policy.
I said it's a dumb question.
I appreciate that.
No, and it's a dumb question.